webmusic.pw 2017-06-06

# MoneyAbility :: Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy 

We are committed to your privacy. This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the MoneyAbility.com website, this includes personal information such as your name, address, phone, email address and credit card information. This also includes third party information such as recipient name, address and phone number.

We use the personal information given when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to deliver the order.

We use the third-party information given when placing an order only to ship the product and confirm delivery. We do not share this information with any outside parties, except to the extent necessary to deliver the order.

Email addresses supplied by you will only be used by MoneyAbility.com for any correspondence needed to complete your order, respond to inquiries you make and to occasionally notify you about the products and services of MoneyAbility.com. Your email address will not be shared with any outside parties.

We are committed to data security. We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and management procedures to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and to insure the appropriate use of the information we collect online. Our checkout process uses industry standard SSL encryption on a secure server to protect the privacy and security of your information.

Our site uses "cookies" to keep track of the items you place in the shopping cart. "Cookies" are harmless, small pieces of data that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive.

Our server captures IP address, browser type and referring URL transmitted by your browser. Your email address is not captured by our server. Email addresses are only captured on the order form and subscribe sign up.

When you click on links within our site that take you to a third-party web site, you will be subject to the third parties' privacy policy. While we support the protection of privacy on the internet, we can not be responsible for the actions of third parties. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of the web sites you visit.

By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by MoneyAbility.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Should you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy and how your information will be used, you may contact us at privacy@moneyability.com.
